<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!--Templates -->

<books>
  <book ID="SECRETGOLDEN QUOTES" Title="SECRETGOLDEN QUOTES">
    <page>I'm becoming! I'M BECOOOOMING!!</page>
    <page>Thou dare inflict thine foul countenance upon mine attention!?</page>
    <page>Now verily, I say not that she labours for precious metals!
Notwithstanding, it is mine observation she doth not engage with individuals lacking means!</page>
    <page>IF YOU SCRATCH MY COOL-ASS LOOKING EXOFRAME I'M TELLING MUM!</page>
    <page>My uncle works atop the spindle and he said this is the best exoframe in all of Qud!</page>
    <page>It's the GOLD for me!</page>
    <page>What do you mean my exoframe can't buy me happiness, do I look sad to you?</page>
    <page>Bwhaa Ha ha ha ha HA HA HA HA HA! Cry some more! HA HA HA HA CRY SOME MORE!</page>
    <page>This exoframe costs 216,000 drams to run for just 3 seconds!</page>
    <page>What!? A Scratch?? My exoframe! WHO'S TOUCHED MY EXOFRAME!?</page>
    <page>I am yet to meet a creature who can outrun FIST!</page>
  </book>

  <book ID="The Becoomer" Title="{{GOLDENSECRET|The Becoomer}}">

    <page>Early in the ascent of the Eaters of Earth to the great glittering weave of the cosmos, hushed wispers turned to frenetic calls to action amongst those in search of the ultimate advancement toward true transhumanism. Questions on the nature of what it means to transcend the human form were vast and varied, and any apparent answers, more varied themselves even than the questions, ammased an exponential blooming of new and weirder questions.

Despite the broad disagreement on near every facet of the subject, perhaps even in spite of it, every academic field concerned with or even remotely adjacent to the subject was in agreement that the term to describe the process of attaining a truly transhuman form was to Become transhuman.

Eons of progress winked by and the field of cybernetics was, amongst the cyberneticists, at the forefront of the race to attaing the first true Becoming. While it was a matter of accepting reality that advancements in genetic engineering were far and away more fruitful in their endeavours, it was not at all difficult to argue that simply becoming less human was mot the same thing as Becoming transhuman.</page>

<page>Cybernetics required a genetically stable host to provide any benefit, and, later, to not quickly poison the host to death, and designing them for the infinity approaching plethora genetic expressions quickly emmerging amongst the population would be an exercise in futility.

Abandoned by the broader academic commiunity, the cyberneticists became a group largely considered crack-pot, holding onto the idea that humanity's next step could be sourced from without rather than within. Their obsession with genetic purity was a relic, but one fully supported by the bredth of scientific achievement and so it was regarded more with side-eyed glances than outright rejection.

Cloning was a simple enough process, and, while it was a mechanism by which genomes were intentionally destabilised, done correctly could, more often than not, preserve the stability of the clonee's genetic make-up. Impefect clones could always be reclaimed for their biological material and new attemps be made.</page>

<page>It was from within this fringe of academic society that Bophades Balles had found his calling. Grabbed by the same enlightened inspiration that had, mere centuries before, inspired the marvel that was Giant Hands, he sought to bring this great boon to the entirety of the human form. Rudimentary work had been done to create powered exoskeletons before but nothing so entirely entwined with the user that it could be considered part of them.

He began what would become his life's work, to bring giganticness to the human form, to transcend humanity's meek size.

To create a Gigantic Exoframe.</page>

<page>The task was not without its perils. Many failed attempts and many reclaimed clones were dashed against the craggy rocks of scientific enquiry, but not for nothing. One day, bathing in the reclaimed biomass of another near-success, Bophades was struck with a relevelation. "Attaining such immense stature can't be done, by implanting a cybernetic into a host. No, instead, the host must be implanted into the cybernetic!"

Bophades Balles jumped from his crimson bath, bits of reclaimed biomass sloughing of his lower half and splatting unceremoniously with each step, and ran immediately to his becoming nook. With a very slight adjustment, and the reckless abandon of someone who's been struck with a glimps of the very making of existence, he implanted himself, not with a Gigantic Exoframe, but into a Gigantic Exoframe.

The nook fired up, working without a hitch. Bophades loudly proclaimed "{{SECRETGOLDEN|I'm gonna Become! Oh high Seraphs above, I'm Becoming!!}}" and then he {{GOLDENSECRET|Became}} all over the place.</page>
  </book>
</books>
